<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Coloradoninjutsu.com]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Coloradoninjutsu.com]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/colorado-ninjutsu/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2015 03:10:18 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/colorado-ninjutsu/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>One on One Ninjutsu Martial Arts & Sword training… Learn from Colorado’s ONLY Certified Master Ninjutsu Instructor… Contact me to apply.   Download Your FREE Training Certificate with Sensei Benson  Name:  Email:      5 Star REviews  "LOVE this place, excellent instruction, fair prices and great people." - Jen "The absolute BEST dojo in Colorado for Ninjutsu and Jujutsu" - Chris Cord "If you're looking for real ninjutsu and jujutsu, then this is the place you need to be" - JD Goodwin read more... “The absolute BEST dojo in Colorado for Ninjutsu and Jujutsu” —Chris Cord Fantastic martial arts are taught there. Not for everybody, if you can’t behave in kids class they won’t train you. Good for them having standards and sticking with them. Same thing in adult classes if you’re a thug or a jerk they ask you not to train, which is great for those of us that want to train with good fun people. Some people might think they are elitists, but since they are the best school that I have trained at they can afford to be. You can’t find a better school in my opinion. —Jen Fairbanks Both of our kids, a girl & boy, have been with Sensei Benson for nearly 10 years. They’ve moved from the kid’s classes to the adult classes and have enjoyed every minute. We “shopped around” at first, but no one came close to Sensei Benson’s approach and expectation for developing the “whole person.” “Kaizen” – or “continuous improvement” is more than a business name here. If you desire the self-discipline of body and mind that authentic martial arts is about, then you can learn it here. My kids developed excellent skills to the point that I worry much less about my daughter walking across her college campus. But my real thanks to Sensei is for their well-developed sense of constant awareness of their surroundings, personal confidence and the impact of their actions on those around them. I give Kaizen Martial Arts an A+++ —Wendy Adams If you’re looking for real ninjutsu and jujutsu, then this is the place you need to be —JD Goodwin Best dojo ever…sometimes funny, always skilled instruction in a discipline that is still an art and hasn’t been watered down into a “sport”. —Daniel Hocker This Martial Arts Studio is the REAL deal! Forget Karate, Kung Fu or TaeKownDo, I’ll take a real Ninja master any day of the week. GREAT instruction, FAIR prices, FUN environment. —Christopher Lee A Message from Sensei Benson</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/colorado-ninjutsu/one-on-one-ninjutsu-martial-arts-and-sword-training-learn-fro/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0d58d17b-1d21-49e6-9a19-1bfce66c44da</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2015 03:09:27 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="http://wolfe.arvixevps.com/~ninjutsu/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/adults-opportunity.png">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/colorado-ninjutsu/about-our-dojo-let-me-introduce-myself-my-name-is-lyle-bens/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">64d6abfe-9566-4a63-8a61-bb5577921a67</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 18:18:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>5 Star REviews  "LOVE this place, excellent instruction, fair prices and great people." - Jen "The absolute BEST dojo in Colorado for Ninjutsu and Jujutsu" - Chris Cord "If you're looking for real ninjutsu and jujutsu, then this is the place you need to be" - JD Goodwin read more...</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/colorado-ninjutsu/5-star-reviews-love-this-place-excellent-instruction-fai/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">eaa2cb45-5417-469f-9b1e-0ee346edf1f1</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 18:18:41 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>The Ninja Dojo, the BEST Martial Arts for kids in Littleton.  Action Packed Martial Arts Busts Boredom! We teach exciting, and engaging Martial Arts classes designed to bring out the best in your child without them becoming bored! Our classes are dynamic, entirely unique and unlike any other martial arts school. We invite you come and watch one of our classes or better yet have your son or daughter try a free class and see why we are so different. Children Need to be Challenged. Have you ever wanted your child to get involved with the martial arts but didn’t know how to start or even if they would like it? Well, we have made it simple for you to decide if our program is right for you. To register for an introductory program all you have to do is pick up the phone and call. One of our friendly instructors will be happy to answer any additional questions that you might have and schedule a time for you to come in and have your child try a free class and see if they like it. Or you can simply register for one of our free intro classes by. What could be simpler than that? If children aren’t challenged they lose interest and fall behind. We’ve all seen it happen. Don’t let it happen to your child. We Divide Our Classes by Age. This Ensures Every Student Receives the Attention they Deserve.  Our Instruction Focuses on Three Key Areas. First: Self-Defense We teach a combination of self-defense techniques, strategy for escaping from danger and getting to safety, and conflict resolution skills. Second: Physical Fitness We emphasize on physical fitness and coordination. In our classes we develop fundamental athletic skills. These are important skills like coordination, flexibility and balance. These skills are required for baseball, soccer, tennis, and more. At Kaizen Martial Arts we teach these skills to each and every student. Whether your child earns his black belt or stops sooner they will have these valuable skills for life! Third: Internal Transformation Not only do we teach the outside physical techniques of martial arts, the punching, kicking and locks, but we also teach the inside skills of the martial arts. These are self-control, self-confidence, and listening skills, as well as proper respect and good manners. What is really powerful about our school is that we don’t just talk to our students about these skills. They actually experience them every single time they attend one of our classes! Soon they learn to apply these same skills in school and in their later life. These are Traditional Lessons that Last a Lifetime. Download Your FREE Training Certificate with Sensei Benson  Name:  Email:      5 Star REviews  "LOVE this place, excellent instruction, fair prices and great people." - Jen "The absolute BEST dojo in Colorado for Ninjutsu and Jujutsu" - Chris Cord "If you're looking for real ninjutsu and jujutsu, then this is the place you need to be" - JD Goodwin read more... “The absolute BEST dojo in Colorado for Ninjutsu and Jujutsu” —Chris Cord Fantastic martial arts are taught there. Not for everybody, if you can’t behave in kids class they won’t train you. Good for them having standards and sticking with them. Same thing in adult classes if you’re a thug or a jerk they ask you not to train, which is great for those of us that want to train with good fun people. Some people might think they are elitists, but since they are the best school that I have trained at they can afford to be. You can’t find a better school in my opinion. —Jen Fairbanks Both of our kids, a girl & boy, have been with Sensei Benson for nearly 10 years. They’ve moved from the kid’s classes to the adult classes and have enjoyed every minute. We “shopped around” at first, but no one came close to Sensei Benson’s approach and expectation for developing the “whole person.” “Kaizen” – or “continuous improvement” is more than a business name here. If you desire the self-discipline of body and mind that authentic martial arts is about, then you can learn it here. My kids developed excellent skills to the point that I worry much less about my daughter walking across her college campus. But my real thanks to Sensei is for their well-developed sense of constant awareness of their surroundings, personal confidence and the impact of their actions on those around them. I give Kaizen Martial Arts an A+++ —Wendy Adams If you’re looking for real ninjutsu and jujutsu, then this is the place you need to be —JD Goodwin Best dojo ever…sometimes funny, always skilled instruction in a discipline that is still an art and hasn’t been watered down into a “sport”. —Daniel Hocker This Martial Arts Studio is the REAL deal! Forget Karate, Kung Fu or TaeKownDo, I’ll take a real Ninja master any day of the week. GREAT instruction, FAIR prices, FUN environment. —Christop</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/colorado-ninjutsu/the-ninja-dojo-the-best-martial-arts-for-kids-in-littleton/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3560e84f-8057-451c-b33a-1ed70af7f771</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 18:18:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Parties & Outings for Birthdays, Schools or Scouts We run fantastic ninja parties that any young ninja would enjoy. Sword fighting, ninja star throwing, obstacle courses, and martial arts, to name a few. Make it more than a party, make it an adventure.   We run one of the best destinations for your school group. Museum tours teach about the history of samurai and the ninja. Trained black belts lead the kids through high energy activities providing a real world context to solidify historical teaching. We provide the perfect balance of education and learning activities guaranteed to be the highlight of your field trip destinations. Our calendar fills up fast each year so contact us now to secure your preferred dates.    History & Martial Arts Anti-Abduction Classes Self-Defense Classes And our award winning Anti-Bullying classes. Learn the Way of the Sword. Have you ever wanted to wield a sword? Of course you have! Now learn the proper way to block, cut and even spar with the Japanese sword. Visit our museum and see the swords and armor from Japan that were used by the Samurai in their life and death encounters. Then step out on the mat for fun exciting but still safe sparring, cutting, and traditional training Katas. Sensei Benson has studied with one of the greatest sword masters in Japan and now you can learn what he was taught.   Download Your FREE Training Certificate with Sensei Benson  Name:  Email:      5 Star REviews  "LOVE this place, excellent instruction, fair prices and great people." - Jen "The absolute BEST dojo in Colorado for Ninjutsu and Jujutsu" - Chris Cord "If you're looking for real ninjutsu and jujutsu, then this is the place you need to be" - JD Goodwin read more... 1234567 See if your date is available now! 303-932-2090   Contact Us</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/colorado-ninjutsu/parties-and-outings-for-birthdays-schools-or-scouts-we-run-fa/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">367f00d8-1ceb-489f-bd09-73ddfda12b3d</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2015 03:09:28 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Home   Why Choose Us?   Contact   About   Adults   Kids   Swordsmanship   Samurai Museum   News   Free Class Why Choose Us? Traditional Martial Arts Traditional Martial Arts. What’s Your Reason? Self defense, fitness, great people, personal development. There are a million reason to start and the benefits are definite and available to anyone. Our Dojo also is one of the few places in the world where you can learn the skills of Ninjutsu. These were the once secret skills of the Japanese Ninja. These skills include not only unarmed combat, but also stealth, weapons and escaping techniques. Classes are fun exciting and open to anyone with the desire to learn. Our class sizes are small and non-athletes are welcomed because our style is not competition based, size and fitness aren’t factors for beginners and progress is individually paced. The Gym is Boring; Martial Arts Isn’t. If you had the opportunity to design the perfect workout it would probably include a bunch of fun and interesting people for starters. The more the merrier right? Then you would plan fun, intense, workouts that would challenge both your mind and body at the same time. Every workout would absolutely enhance your flexibility, dexterity, and strength, while revealing valuable aspects about yourself. All the while, you’re learning how to protect yourself and those around you. If that’s anywhere close to how you would design the perfect workout, then you have just described classes at Kaizen Martial Arts. Here, we teach traditional Ninjutsu and we invite you to join us. It’s easy. Simply contact us or set up a free class. Try it and decide for yourself. What could be simpler?   Download Your FREE Training Certificate with Sensei Benson  Name:  Email:      5 Star REviews  "LOVE this place, excellent instruction, fair prices and great people." - Jen "The absolute BEST dojo in Colorado for Ninjutsu and Jujutsu" - Chris Cord "If you're looking for real ninjutsu and jujutsu, then this is the place you need to be" - JD Goodwin read more... “The absolute BEST dojo in Colorado for Ninjutsu and Jujutsu” —Chris Cord Fantastic martial arts are taught there. Not for everybody, if you can’t behave in kids class they won’t train you. Good for them having standards and sticking with them. Same thing in adult classes if you’re a thug or a jerk they ask you not to train, which is great for those of us that want to train with good fun people. Some people might think they are elitists, but since they are the best school that I have trained at they can afford to be. You can’t find a better school in my opinion. —Jen Fairbanks Both of our kids, a girl & boy, have been with Sensei Benson for nearly 10 years. They’ve moved from the kid’s classes to the adult classes and have enjoyed every minute. We “shopped around” at first, but no one came close to Sensei Benson’s approach and expectation for developing the “whole person.” “Kaizen” – or “continuous improvement” is more than a business name here. If you desire the self-discipline of body and mind that authentic martial arts is about, then you can learn it here. My kids developed excellent skills to the point that I worry much less about my daughter walking across her college campus. But my real thanks to Sensei is for their well-developed sense of constant awareness of their surroundings, personal confidence and the impact of their actions on those around them. I give Kaizen Martial Arts an A+++ —Wendy Adams If you’re looking for real ninjutsu and jujutsu, then this is the place you need to be —JD Goodwin Best dojo ever…sometimes funny, always skilled instruction in a discipline that is still an art and hasn’t been watered down into a “sport”. —Daniel Hocker This Martial Arts Studio is the REAL deal! Forget Karate, Kung Fu or TaeKownDo, I’ll take a real Ninja master any day of the week. GREAT instruction, FAIR prices, FUN environment. —Christopher Lee A Message from Sensei Benson Click here for a Special Video Message for you… Listen Here Be Sociable, Share!   inShare</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/colorado-ninjutsu/home-why-choose-us-contact-about-adults-kids-sw/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5d74dff4-109d-448c-85d5-dcd9d730fac8</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 18:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Home   Why Choose Us?   Contact   About   Adults   Kids   Swordsmanship   Samurai Museum   News   Free Class 1234  Come Visit our Martial Arts Studio in Littleton …enjoy a Martial Arts class, on me! Download Your FREE Training Certificate with Sensei Benson  Name:  Email:      5 Star REviews  "LOVE this place, excellent instruction, fair prices and great people." - Jen "The absolute BEST dojo in Colorado for Ninjutsu and Jujutsu" - Chris Cord "If you're looking for real ninjutsu and jujutsu, then this is the place you need to be" - JD Goodwin read more... Martial Arts For Adults Classes are fun, exciting, and open to anyone with the desire to learn. Our Dojo is also one of the few places in the world where you can learn the skills of Ninjutsu. These were the once secrets skills of the Japanese Ninja. These skills include not only unarmed combat, but also stealth, weapons and escaping techniques. Our step by step process allows anyone to succeed. Check us out and see for yourself. Get a FREE class here…  Kids LOVE Our Classes You’ll love what we do for your child in our school. Improved confidence and self esteem is a gift that lasts for a lifetime. Martial arts is absolutely the best way for a child to learn both. Make the time and we guarantee that you won’t be disappointed by our first class facility, dynamic instructors and our top of the line customer service. We all know the rewards of having a child involved in martial arts. Why not give your child those advantages starting today? Bring your child by for a free, no obligation, class and see if martial arts is a good fit. Learn more here…  A Message from Sensei Benson Click here for a Special Video Message for you… Listen Here Be Sociable, Share!   inShare</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/colorado-ninjutsu/home-why-choose-us-contact-about-adults-kids-sw/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f4de6527-e672-40ab-b664-48212814f02e</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 18:12:46 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="http://wolfe.arvixevps.com/~ninjutsu/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/kids-home-img.png">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/colorado-ninjutsu/891d361b-e5ea-48b9-9322-2f4843501588/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">891d361b-e5ea-48b9-9322-2f4843501588</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 05:21:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>"LOVE this place, excellent instruction, fair prices and great people." - Jen "The absolute BEST dojo in Colorado for Ninjutsu and Jujutsu" - Chris Cord "If you're looking for real ninjutsu and jujutsu, then this is the place you need to be" - JD Goodwin read more...</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/colorado-ninjutsu/love-this-place-excellent-instruction-fair-prices-and-gre/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7a28881e-9fa2-498f-8f66-44c02a3d6fa8</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 05:14:09 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The greatest martial art in the world]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The greatest martial art in the world</h1><p>Ninjutsu is the greatest martial art in the world</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/colorado-ninjutsu/the-greatest-martial-art-in-the-world/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">94d68734-f901-4491-9744-16bd560da5a8</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 04:55:13 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>